我把你的配菜扔了
I threw away your garnish!
该死
Damn it!
-上菜了  -上菜
- Order up! - Order up!
琳  把这端给亨利
Lin, take this to Henry!
不  琳达  那这端给亨利
No, Linda. Take this to Henry!
除非你两和好
I'm not taking anything anywhere
不然我哪份也不拿
until you two make peace!
知道你们需要什么吗
You know what you need?
来吧  各位  唱起来
Come on, people! Sing!
我们让这两个家伙和好如初
We can bring these guys back together!
*和气  和气  和气*
*Peace, peace, peace*
和气  和气  各位
Peace, peace... Everybody!
和气  和气  唱起来
Peace, peace...  Come on.
*和气  和气  和…*
*Peace, peace, pea...
快  和气
Yeah! Peace
得  我自己端给亨利
Fine, I'll take it to Henry myself!
我也是
Then I will, too!
把你的脚拿...
Get your foot out of my...
来嘛  今天可是圣诞节
Come on, it's Christmas!
给  亨利  老样子
Here you go, Henry. The usual.
给  亨利
Here you go, Henry.
"宝贝开我的车吧"汉堡
The "Baby You Can Chive My Car Burger."